A Guide to the Rodman C. Rockefeller papers FA1350
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Personal Interests, 1929-2005; III; 14.41 Cubic Feet 32 letter document boxes, 2 legal document boxes, and 1 record storage box
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller and Sascha M. Rockefeller Philanthropy Yearbook, 1989-1990; 1995; 1997 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1996 January-June (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1996 July-December (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1997 January-May (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1997 June-December (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Madeline Cremers, 1997 March-1999 July (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1998 January-June (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1998 July-December (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1999 January-June (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1999 July-December (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Atlantic Productions, (Anthony Geffen), Correspondence, 1992-1994 March 4 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Atlantic Productions, (Anthony Geffen), Correspondence, 1994 January-August (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Atlantic Productions, (Anthony Geffen), Correspondence, 1994 September-December (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Atlantic Productions, (Anthony Geffen), Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Easter and Birthday Letters, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Itineraries, 1980-1986 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Itineraries, 1982; 1987 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Itineraries, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Itineraries, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Itineraries, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Itineraries, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Itineraries, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Itineraries, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Itineraries, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Itineraries, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Itineraries, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Itineraries, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Itineraries, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Itineraries, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - S.M. Rockefeller and Rodman C. Rockefeller Itineraries, 2000 January-November (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller Family Documentary, The American Experience, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - International Skye Associates, Peter A. White, 1993-1996 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - 1993 World Pairs Championship and Board, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - NAR Biographer, Cary Reich, 1989; 1995-1996 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Sailboat Charter, 1989-1996 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Intellectual Property, 1996-1997 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Harbor Club, Seal Island, Maine, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Lincoln Kirstein, 1982-1989 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Long Island University - Student Sponsorship, 1985-1987 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Ballynahinch Castle, 1984-2000 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Somes Sound, Maine, 1981-1994 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Dinner Parties, 1981-1982 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Dinner Parties, 1979-1980 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1954-1969 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - The Fifth Paper, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Honorariums, Gifts etc., 1944-1975 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - United States Equestrian Team, Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Shingle Island, Maine - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Shingle Island, Maine - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Barbara O. Rockefeller Memorial, 1986 January-February (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Barbara O. Rockefeller Memorial, 1986 February (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Winterburn, Lo -Yi, Chen, Architect, 1985-1988 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Memorial Garden Organization of American States, 1983-1985 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Sergeant Point Property, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Honorarium, 1979; 1980 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Bequest, 1980 January 29 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Monte Sacro - Venezuela, 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Freedom Award, 1979 October 18 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Winterburn Correspondence, 1976-1987 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - North Hollow Development Partnership, 1969-1996 (Box 49, Folder 18-18A)
  - Gifts to Rodman C. Rockefeller from Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1957 April 25 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Correspondence, 1956; 1958 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Purchase of IBEC Stock by Rodman C. Rockefeller from Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1957 February (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Correspondence with Rodman C. Rockefeller, 1955-1960 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Correspondence with Rodman C. Rockefeller, 1955-1956 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Home and Garden Magazine - Rockefeller Tavern, 1992 April (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - "A Brief History of the Rockefeller Tavern and Surrounding Property", 1740 -1986 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - U.S. Army, 1955-1956 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Atlantic Productions - Anthony Geffen - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Percy and Bessy Scrapbook - Clark Christmas Dinner, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Cousin Yearbook, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Metzler Correspondence, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Metzler Correspondence, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Metzler Correspondence, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Metzler Correspondence, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Metzler Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Metzler Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Metzler Correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller Financial Services, Long Range Planning, 1989-1990 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller and Alexandra "Sascha" Metzler Rockefeller's Wedding, 1980 June 13 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller and Alexandra "Sascha" Metzler Rockefeller's Wedding, 1980 June 13 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Letters and Clippings, 1961-1962 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Mary C. Rockefeller, 1932 April 26 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Meile L. Rockefeller, 1979-1988 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Laura Spencer Rockefeller article, 2004 June (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Michael S. Rockefeller, 1980-1996 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Peter C. Rockefeller, 1984-1998 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Stuart A. Rockefeller, 1981-1995 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - The Descendants of William Avery and Eliza Davidson Rockefeller and Their Families, 1810-1970 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Cousins' Philanthropy Yearbook, Second Edition, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Cousins' Philanthropy Yearbook, Second Edition, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller Benefit, 1995 June 27 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller, Fellowship Conference, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship Conference, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship Conference, 1989 February-July (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship Conference, 1989 February-July (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship Conference, 1989 June-December (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship Conference, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship Conference, 1990 March-June (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship Conference, 1990 March-June (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship Conference, 1991 July-December (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship Conference, 1991 July-December (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship Conference, 1990-1991 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship Conference, 1991 May-June (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship Conference, 1990-1991 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship Conference, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship Conference, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship Conference, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship Resumes, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship 25th Anniversary, Rodman C. Rockefeller Speech, 1990 October 12 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship Section Committee Winners, 1995 June 7 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Michael C. Rockefeller Papers, Transfer to the Rockefeller Archive Center, 1988-1989 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - The Michael C. Rockefeller Memorial Fellowship, 25th Anniversary Fund Booklet (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - The Michael C. Rockefeller Memorial Fellowship, 25th Anniversary Fund, 1990 October (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship 25th Anniversary, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller - Fellowship 25th Anniversary, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - M.C.R. Fellowship - 5th Anniversary Booklets (Box 53)
  - Autograph Book (Box 53)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Special Studies Project Reports (Box 53)
  - Art and Architecture publications (Box 54)
  - Pocantico Park Proposal (Box 54)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller - Rolodex and Information Cards (Box 55)
  - Christmas Card Master List, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Family Christmas Lunch, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Christmas Card List, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Christmas Card List, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller's 60th Birthday, 1992 April 24 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller's 50th Birthday, 1992 April 24 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Remarks at the Wedding of Steven and Barbara Rockefeller, Vermont, 1991 May 10 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Dinner: 10th Anniversary, 1990 June 13 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Sascha and Rodman Rockefeller's Wedding, 1980 June 13 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Sascha and Rodman Rockefeller's Wedding - Cards, Notes and Well Wishes for the Bride and Groom, 1980 June 13 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Peter C. Rockefeller's 40th Birthday, New York, 1997 March 5 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Remarks on the 80th Birthday of March Clark Rockefeller, Maine, 1987 June (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Mary C. Rockefeller Memorial (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Dedication of Nelson A. Rockefeller Park, Battery Park City, New York, 1996 June 12 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Casita Maria Fiesta 1995 - Plaza Hotel, NY, 1995 October 25 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Phelps Memorial Hospital to Honor Rockefeller Family, Purchase, New York, 1991 November 16 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Family Service of Westchester - Family of the Year Award, Sleepy Hollow, NY, 1988 June 1 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Sewells Falls Interview, Boston Globe, 1984 May 25 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Dedication of NAR Center for the Social Sciences - Dartmouth College, 1983 September 24 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Winterburn Correspondence, 1976-1986 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous, 2000-2001 (Box 57, Folder 1-4)
  - Correspondence, 2000 January-May 14 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Death Certificates Birth and Marriage (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Funeral, 2000 May 18 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Memorial Service, 2000 June 1 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Obituaries, Publications (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Condolences (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Condolences to address and mail (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Condolences (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Condolences Answered (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Condolence Letters (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Condolence Letters, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Memorial Service for Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1979 February 21 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Darmouth, 34th Reunion, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - New York Blood Center - Annual Reports, 1993-1996 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Planning Board of the Town of Mount Pleasant (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller Memorial Service (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Michael C. Rockefeller Misc. (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Mary Morgan, David Callard (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Steven R. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Ann Rockefeller Roberts (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Michael and Tara (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Stuart R. (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Peter and Allison (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Meile R. (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Barbara Olson Rockefeller (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Laurance Rockefeller (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - David Rockefeller (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Peggy and David Rockefeller (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Family Members (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Rockefeller Family I (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Rockefeller Family Ancestors (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Playhouse Matter - Rockefeller Family - Future of Pocantico Estate (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Alex Alexander (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1995 July-December (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1995 January-June (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1994 July-December (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1994 January-June (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1993 July-December (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1993 January-June (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1992 July-December (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1992 January-June (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1991 July-December (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1991 January-June (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1990 July-December (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1990 January-June (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1986 July-December (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1986 January-June (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1985 July-December (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1985 January-June (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1984 July-December (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1984 January-June (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1983 July-December (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1983 January-June (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Correspondence, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Notes, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Awards given to Rodman C. Rockefeller and Nelson A. Rockefeller (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - MCR - Resolution, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Childhood (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - JDR 3rd Condolence Letters, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Blanchette Rockefeller, 1992 November 29 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Letter to NAR from his Mother, 1929 September 25 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Condolence Letters, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Condolence Letters (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Memorial Service, 1979 February 2 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1979 January 26 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Memorial Clippings and Honors (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Nelson Rockefeller and Jr. (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller's Letters to his Mother, 1951-1955 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - MCR Condolence Letters (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - MCR Personal Correspondence (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Rodman C. Rockefeller Cards, 2000 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Press Clippings (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Research for Possible Book on Nelson A. Rockefeller (Box 66, Folder 1-4)
  - Non Profit Organizations (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Interview with Cary Reich, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller Group Photo (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Photos (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Sascha Rockefeller (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - MoMA Correspondence, 1990-1998 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Biocyte Chronological, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Phelps Correspondence, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Shipley School Lunch at Playhouse, 1995 June 7 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Mrs. Sascha Rockefeller's Shipley Reunion, Lunch at the River House, 1993 April 1 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Sascha and Rodman Wedding, 1980 June 13 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Speeches, collected by Rodman C. Rockefeller, 1940-1998 (Box 67, Folder 8-25)
  - Speeches, collected by Rodman C. Rockefeller, 1940-1998 (Box 69, Folder 1-21)
  - Personal - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Inter-American Goodwill through Sports and Music, Latin America, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Mary Toddhunter Clark Rockefeller (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller - Handwritten Notes (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Gladstone Driving Event, 1998 May 30-31 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Jordan House, Seal Harbor, Maine, 1980 September (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller 50th Birthday, 1982 April 24 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Atlantic Productions, (Anthony Geffen), Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - North Hollow Development Partnership Photographs, 1986 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 82, Folder 12)
- Political Interests, 1964-1998; IV; 1.23 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes and 1 legal document box
  - New York State Republican Hall of Honor Dinner, 1990 February 27 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - President George H.W. Bush's Inauguration - Washington D.C. (US Council of the Mexico -US Business Community), 1989 January 18-21 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Fund Raising Reception for Andrew O'Rourke, Republican Gubernatorial Candidate - Winterburn Farm, 1986 October 15 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Republican Club Lincoln Day Dinner, 1981-1985 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Republican National Hispanic Assembly - Viva '84, 1984 May 24 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - White House Dinner - President Reagan, 1984 May 4 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Prime Minister Denise Thatcher Dinner, 1983 July 7 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Luncheon for President Mohamed Siad Barre of Somalia - Pocantico Hills, New York, 1982 March 21 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Senator Javits Reception, 1980 September 28 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Commission on U.S. Brazilian Relations - Mission to Sao Paulo and Brasilia, Brazil, 1981 August 9-12 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - New York Republican State Commission - Policy Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Political Contributions - MODRN PAC, 1983-1987 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Political Contributions, 1964-1985 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Political Contributions, 1986-1988 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Political Contributions, 1989-1998 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Political Contributions, 1986-1998 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Pierre Rinfret Campaign, 1990-1991 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Republican State Finance Committee, 1986-1990 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - New York State - Republican Committee - Empire Club, 1985-1990 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Political - General, 1982-1998 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Political - General, 1982-1998 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Bill Green Advisory Committee, 1982-1990 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Westchester County Republican Committee, 1982-1990 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Roy Goodman "The Elephants" Group, 1982-1986 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Republican Congressional Leadership Council, 1983-1988 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Foreign Affairs, Washington D.C., 1969 August 19 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Remarks on NAFTA - Congressional Meeting (Speech), 1993 November 4 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Op -Ed Article - NAFTA - "Best Deal Ever", San Antonio Express - News, 1993 October 7 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - NY Republican Hall of Honor Dinner, New York, 1990 February 27 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Introduction of Minister Campillo Sainz of Mexico, Council of the Americas, Plaza Hotel, New York, 1974 December 5 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Introduction of Senator Jacob K. Javits - Adela 10th Anniversary - New York, 1974 November (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - New York State - Republican Committee, Empire Club, 1985-1990 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Educational Interests, 1956-2001; V; 4.74 Cubic Feet 10 letter document boxes and 2 legal document boxes
  - Institute of International Education - Strategic Development, 1999-2000 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Institute of International Education - Rededication of Conference Rooms in Honor of Rodman C. Rockefeller and Mary Clark Rockefeller, 2000 September-October (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Institute of International Education - Rededication of Conference Rooms in Honor of Rodman C. Rockefeller and Mary Clark Rockefeller, 2000 September-October (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Institute of International Education - 80th Dinner Celebration, 1999 October 14 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Institute of International Education - 80th Dinner Celebration, 1999 October 14 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Institute of International Education - San Francisco Dinner, 1999 September 15-17 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Institute of International Education - Goodman Dinner, 1999 June 1 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Institute of International Education - Goodman Dinner, 1999 June 1 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Institute of International Education - Fulbright Dinner, 1999 May 6 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Institute of International Education - New York and the World Celebration Dinner, Plaza Hotel, 1997 December 3 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Institute of International Education - By -Laws, 1997 January 27 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Institute of International Education - Board of Trustees, Signed Trustee Appeal Letters, 1998 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Institute of International Education - Board of Trustees for 1999, Signed Trustee Appeal Letters, 1999 April (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Institute of International Education - Director of Development Job Search, 1999 February-July (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Institute of International Education - Presidential Search, 1998 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    Restricted - Open in 2028
  - Institute of International Education - Presidential Candidates, 1998 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Institute of International Education - Fulbright Legacy Fund, 1998-2000 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Institute of International Education - Fund Raising Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 72, Folder 18)